onlycashsurveys.com 2019-06-27

# Only Cash Surveys Privacy Policy

|  |   
---  
|  |  |  |  |   
---|---|---|---|---  
  
|  OnlyCashSurveys Privacy Policy  
---  
  
OnlyCashSurveys is committed to safeguarding your privacy online. Please read the following policy to understand how your personal information will be treated as you make full use of our website and services. 

OnlyCashSurveys adheres to the principles set forth in the Safe Harbor framework as established by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personally identifiable information provided to OnlyCashSurveys from the European Union. 

What personally identifiable information does OnlyCashSurveys collect from me? 
     OnlyCashSurveys collects information in several ways from different parts of our network of websites. 

Some personal information is gathered when you register. During registration, OnlyCashSurveys asks for your name, email address, zip code, household information and personal interests. The more information you volunteer (and the more accurate it is), the better we are able to customize your experience. Once you register you are no longer anonymous to OnlyCashSurveys - use to access the various protected areas of the site.Also, if you contact OnlyCashSurveys we may keep a record of that correspondence.Whenever OnlyCashSurveys collects personal information we make an effort to include a link to this Privacy Policy on that page. 

What are cookies and how does OnlyCashSurveys use them? 
     A cookie is a small amount of data that is sent to your browser from a web server and stored on your computer's hard drive. As part of offering and providing customizable and personalized services, OnlyCashSurveys may use cookies to store and sometimes track information about you. Some areas on OnlyCashSurveys where you are prompted to log-in or that are customizable may require that you accept cookies. This avoids you having to enter your login information many times in one day. 
Who is collecting information and for what purpose? 
     OnlyCashSurveys collects valuable information which assists in developing new products and services. When you are on a OnlyCashSurveys site and are asked for personal information, you are sharing that information with OnlyCashSurveys alone, unless it is specifically stated otherwise. If data is being collected and/or maintained by any company other than OnlyCashSurveys -- or its parent company UnitedSample,Inc. , you will be notified prior to the time of the data collection or transfer. If you do not want your data to be shared, you can choose not to allow the transfer by not using that particular service. 

Promotions that run on OnlyCashSurveys may be sponsored by companies other than OnlyCashSurveys or may be co-sponsored by OnlyCashSurveys and another company. Some or all data collected during a promotion may be shared with the sponsor. If data will be shared, you will be notified prior to the time of data collection or transfer. You can decide not to participate in the promotion if you do not want your data to be shared. 

Any Sensitive Information (i.e. personal information specifying medical or health conditions, racial or ethnic origin, political opinions, religious or philosophical beliefs, trade union membership or information specifying the sex life of the individual) will be treated with additional care. If OnlyCashSurveys intends to disclose such information to a third party or use it for a different purpose than originally collected, then you will be expressly asked permission prior to any such disclosure. 

Please be aware that OnlyCashSurveys advertisers or websites that have links on our site may collect personally identifiable information about you. The information practices of those websites linked to OnlyCashSurveys are not covered by this privacy statement. 

With whom does OnlyCashSurveys share my information? 
     As a general rule, OnlyCashSurveys will not disclose any of your personally identifiable information except when we have your permission or under special circumstances, such as when we believe in good faith that the law requires it or under the circumstances described below. 

Please see the Terms of Service or User Agreements for each of our products and services for more detailed information about how your personal information may be shared. The following describes some of the ways that your information may be disclosed. 

Business Partners & Sponsors: 
     OnlyCashSurveys may disclose your personal information to business partners or sponsors, but this is specifically described to you prior to data collection or prior to transferring the data. If any personal data about you were ever to be shared, we will tell you before we collect or transfer the data. 

Many promotions offer opportunities to request additional information from sponsors. By requesting more information, you give OnlyCashSurveys permission to transfer your personal information to the sponsor so they can fulfill your request. In many instances, only your email address will be shared. If more information will be shared with the sponsor, you will be notified prior to the transfer. 

Sharing   
We partner with another party to provide specific services. When the user signs up for these services, we will share names, or other contact information that is necessary for the third party to provide these services. We provide data with our partners only when our users select the services of our partners when they register. This is done by opting in or not opting out of their service. If you opt-in to our newsletter, we may partner with outside firms which will send out third party offers. We share information gathered with partners that you select during the registration process. We may send you offers on behalf of other third parties. If we partner with other 3rd parties to send you offers, you will be given the opportunity to opt-out at any time. These parties are not allowed to use personally identifiable information except for the purpose of providing these services. 

Third Party Data & Data in the Aggregate: 
     Under confidentiality agreements, OnlyCashSurveys may match user information with third party data. Also, OnlyCashSurveys discloses aggregated user statistics (for example, 45% of our users are female) in order to describe our services to prospective partners, advertisers, and other third parties, and for other lawful purposes. 

Other: OnlyCashSurveys may also disclose account information in special cases when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be violating OnlyCashSurveyss Terms of Service or may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) OnlyCashSurveyss rights or property, other OnlyCashSurveys users, or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities. OnlyCashSurveys may disclose or access account information when we believe in good faith that the law requires it and for administrative and other purposes that we deem necessary to maintain, service, and improve our products and services. 

What are my choices regarding collection, use, and distribution of my information? 
     Only OnlyCashSurveys (or agents working on behalf of OnlyCashSurveys and under confidentiality agreements) will send you these direct mailings and only if you indicated that you do not object to these offers. 

You also have choices with respect to cookies. By modifying your browser preferences, you have the choice to accept all cookies, to be notified when a cookie is set, or to reject all cookies. If you choose to reject all cookies you will be unable to use those OnlyCashSurveys services that require registration in order to participate. 

What is OnlyCashSurveys' policy on allowing me to update, correct, or delete my personally identifiable information? 
     You may edit your OnlyCashSurveys Account Information and your public OnlyCashSurveys Profile at any time by using your OnlyCashSurveys ID and password. If you have forgotten your password, please click here. 

Your OnlyCashSurveys account can be deleted or deactivated. Please contact [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#1c6f696c6c736e685c737270657f7d6f746f696e6a79656f327f7371) for further instructions about deleting or deactivating your OnlyCashSurveys account. 

What security precautions are in place to protect the loss, misuse, or alteration of my information? 
     Your OnlyCashSurveys Account Information and OnlyCashSurveys Profile are password-protected so that you and only you have access to this personal information. 

We recommend that you do not divulge your password to anyone. OnlyCashSurveys will never ask you for your password in an unsolicited phone call or in an unsolicited email. Also remember to sign out of your OnlyCashSurveys account and close your browser window when you have finished your work. This is to ensure that others cannot access your personal information and correspondence if you share a computer with someone else or are using a computer in a public place like a library or Internet cafe. 

Whenever OnlyCashSurveys handles personal information as described above, regardless of where this occurs, OnlyCashSurveys takes steps to ensure that your information is treated securely and in accordance with the relevant Terms of Service and this Privacy Policy. 

Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, OnlyCashSurveys cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us or from our online products or services, and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission, we make our best effort to ensure its security on our systems. 

What else should I know about my privacy? 
     Please keep in mind that whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information online - for example on message boards, through email, or in chat areas - that information can be collected and used by others. In short, if you post personal information online that is accessible to the public, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return. 

Ultimately, you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your passwords and/or any account information. Please be careful and responsible whenever you're online. 

You can reach New OCS LLC at 56 Upland Ct, Newark DE 19713 

By signing up for our services, you agree to receive our newsletter and offers to take surveys and other money making opportunities. If you do not wish to receive these e-mails, you may opt-out at any time, by clicking on the opt-out link in the e-mail messages you receive. 

Additional information 
     Questions regarding this statement should be directed to [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#88fbfdf8f8e7fafcc8e7e6e4f1ebe9fbe0fbfdfafeedf1fba6ebe7e5). 
|   
|  |
